we aren't good right shut up and our
master Mirotic yonder dealership yeah
buddy
the Hyundai dealer shhh
all right we're in HD a mode ok doing
something
perfectly straight line when John died
HTA
we think I'm telling nectar person on
Twitter first you to live
[Music]
you got a few discard we have 14 14 so I
think we got to go back soon we don't up
for too many miles on this car pretty
good though it's pretty good let's see
if we get like anything at all that's
hard
which bank to be robbed yeah that's a
good question
they said you'd go 163 will it make a
turn pretty good
long did it do it yeah all right now
let's let's take trying to have it do
some a little art let's go here Oh God
what model Sonata Limited 2020 oh god
that's so terrifying
it does not make turns doing something
yeah that Lexus is like screw you we get
it
I don't let its key thing about now oh
it's detecting that thar line is a lame
wait this is actually really concerning
its steering right now is it yeah how I
disengaged
the mode confusion on this is
unbelievable I just take the next exit
what is that sound we don't know what
was that sound
[Music]
assisting because it thought that the
crack in the pavement was a lane or
service lane departure warning
Thank You Congrats in the profitable
quarter yes thank you thank you
wait so next exit soon there's like
points
because cars kid
this later equality can they make a turn
how does driver hit monitoring handle
masks farewell
[Music]
okay
let's move down to 31 we want to go
right or left let go left or right left
and it does not continue yeah wouldn't
have seen that car you think but look at
this cool thing you guys Oh with the
blinkers they have the okay look at that
they have the camera yeah
does this one I've stop and go
definitely this is Sean guys I think
it's the same one that's on the palisade
so it is their highest end it has this
always on seems like a very it seems
like Oh
adaptive cruise has anything to do with
that well
just for our enjoyment Hey oh yeah it
gets a higher trim you get a smaller
engine and it's actually slower I think
gonna gives us more gas higher trim
slower
I love slower engine you said he has
like a 1.6 liter turbo engine look at
that space back there for Willam so much
room so much room in this car crazy
oh wow
[Music]
delayed reaction what's assisting Haley
yes you want to take the exit valve
little out Avenue oh yeah
[Music]
it's good at straight lines though don't
ask it for like torpor like this it
probably will be okay
[Music]
I know it's stabbing me
wait why does it nag you because you
haven't touched the wheel in a while
[Music]
that's pretty good yeah yeah I'd say so
like this straight line I'd say it's
pretty close to open pilot - I mean
everybody can do this train long doing
nothing yeah they're just - just let me
drift over that line
I'm still not sure and hear it but it
won't do well okay okay West yeah so if
you're coming at all in an angle to the
lines it doesn't seem to do anything it
seems to be very like they seem to have
a very sort of it's interesting I mean
this was one of the things discussed in
the in the safety discussions on costume
Forks about whether cars can steer
[Music]
without being engaged and they seem to
take the philosophy that you can but
they're steering codes are incredibly
weak so we cut it doesn't seem like like
like we'll do anything here it won't
yeah like the steering wheel needs to be
green on the dash
and laughed at the line so now what if I
like its flashing green it's a nice off
so now it's off so it's green like locks
on I say it was just green man okay
that's interesting
oh well like it's good mom yeah yeah no
he gets good marks yeah well so yeah we
learned yesterday that there's a some
entrepreneurial South Korean I'm not
gonna say anything about I don't know if
they're care an adult or a man or a
woman who's been testing out I think I
took nothing literally took nothing
[Music]
who's been who's been doing free on
installation services around South Korea
got a fork Hsu mm mm yeah Wow got a four
why isn't George wearing a comma hoodie
wait wait calm hoodies like that
everyone would wear them by this car
guys for what it's worth
Erik Morocco says South Korea has been
buying a ton of pandas from me oh
they're buying panda that's what they do
it yeah that makes sense yeah yeah yeah
don't buy a white panda you're gonna be
very disappointed when open 5:08 comes
out about zero way it's gonna require
the GPS
GPS Aston Martin stop there yeah we just
have oh I guess it has smart Park so
it's not like Park Assist I haven't seen
it put any big big torque on the
steering but here's another reason we're
buying this car
Yandex is now using them in Russia as
their base platform for their level 4 so
this will be kamas base platform for our
let's just say full self-driving before
is a stupid toy
just just do it Yandex does you're sorry
so I'm locked on right now does this
mean I guess I don't even need the
cruise control to use this
see there's on the right you're right
the Subaru oh yeah yeah Mabel are on the
other side yeah that's terrible
all right this is let's see what does
this turn yeah this intersection
all right lost it in the intersection
it's like oh it's the green thing okay
okay at least the green thing is helpful
for you as the driver you know I kind of
missed uh like a deep or something
didn't you notice the same system where
I so log on but then it beeps when it
locks up so you know it's gonna work
hmm that oh yeah oh well it separates
the steering from there longer No
it is nice we shall show the broken trip
yeah it has a broken trim see this is a
new card some serious production
problems like things falling off why
wait let's try some our park yeah so I
turn it on sorry you guys I'm like
shaking this okay it's on I press this
button use forward a backward button on
smart key after leaving vehicle so we
have to leave okay I'm not staying in
eat kidding me what if it crashes
I'll stay in this is a little wearing
this car might be moving oh yeah yeah
and George is using this with the remote
well there you go
that make sense yeah I've got a die at
some point you guys that's not bad
not really try it's also aggressive with
the brakes
a little not really not from what I saw
you can say it's pretty straight Oh Oh
interesting
all right the sales department is open
because we learned that and they are a
essential business sales department is
an essential business you guys that's
pretty fun to be in the air look at that
though fun
very nice masterpiece